Jacek Szubert

Experienced DevOps engineer focused on cloud computing, managing infrastructure as a code, automatization of software integration and deployment process and configuration management.

Key technologies: Linux, AWS, Docker, Ansible, Chef, Python.

Relocating to Australia at the end of December - open for both permanent and contract jobs starting from January 2017.

Experience

2016-still **DevOps Engineer (freelance)**, eHealth Systems Africa, Berlin (Germany).

Working on multiple cloud-based projects supporting public health in Western Africa. Implementing and optimizing infrastructure management approach, deployment strategies, monitoring solutions, mitigating security risks, reducing infrastructure costs.

2015–2016 **DevOps Engineer**, *SoftServe*, Wroclaw (Poland).

Developing cloud based infrastructure and CI & CD pipelines for web services.

2013–2015 **Software Integration Engineer (SCM)**, *Nokia / Nokia Solutions and Networks*, Wroclaw (Poland).

Technical leader for DevOps/SysAdmin teams responsible for two projects.

- Administration of physical and virtualised servers and storages.
- Administration of Linux systems, including usage of configuration management tools.
- Scripting in Bash and Python.
- \circ Developing and optimizing continous integration flows and release processes of C/C++ and Java projects.
- Quality assurance analysis using SonarQube, preparation for TL9000 audit.
- Taking over a project from other company, responsible for both competence and infrastructure transfer.
- 2012 **OSS Technical Support internship**, *Nokia Siemens Networks*, Wroclaw (Poland).

Local laboratory administration, basic configuration and verification of OSS systems.

Education

2013–2015 Master's degree, Wroclaw University of Technology.

Telecommunication — Mobile Networks.

2009–2013 **Bachelor's degree**, Wroclaw University of Technology.

Electronics and Telecommunication — Information and Communication Networks.

Languages

english professional working proficiency

IELTS

polish native

Skills

administration Linux - RHEL and Debian based distributions, CoreOS.

cloud computing Amazon Web Services - wide variety of services including development of serverless

tools, deploying infrastructure with CloudFormation and Beanstalk, managing

containers with ECS.

Eucalyptus.

cm Ansible, Chef, basics of Puppet.

containers Docker.

scripting Bash, Python (including libraries like Boto3, docker-py, Flask, SQLAlchemy, basics

of Django).

monitoring NewRelic, Librato, CloudWatch.

vcs GIT, Subversion.

ci Jenkins, Travis CI.

virtualization Citrix XenServer, VMware vSphere.

networking Practical understanding of TCP/IP networks, configuring network elements, trou-

bleshooting; VPCs.

rdms Administration of PostgreSQL, basics of SQL.

nosql & bigdata Basics of administration of CouchDB and ELK stack.

code analysis SonarQube and related tools.

hardware HP Server Hardware, NetApp.

Trainings and certifications

cloud computing AWS Certified Developer – Associate.

AWS-ADEV-3416

embedded Designing Embedded Systems with Yocto (Doulos).

networking Cisco Certified Network Associate.

english IELTS general training certification (C1).